<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="@drawable/howtoplaybg"
    tools:context=".HOWTOPLAY">


    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="393dp"
        android:layout_height="308dp"
        android:layout_marginBottom="96dp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toTopOf="@+id/btnBack2"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintHorizontal_bias="0.0"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent">

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/tvGameInstructions"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:fontFamily="@font/samurai2"
            android:textColor="#8f6233"
            android:padding="40dp"
            android:text="Objective:\n\nHone your ninja memory skills by mastering the art of adding fading numbers! As you progress through different levels, the challenge intensifies. Are you ready to become a true ninja mathematician?\n\nLevel 1: Beginner - Add 3 Numbers\n\nA set of three numbers will appear on the screen.\nMemorize the numbers quickly before they start to fade.\nOnce the numbers fade, recall and add them together.\nType your answer and press 'Enter' to check if you're correct.\nMaster this level to unlock the next challenge!\n\nLevel 2: Novice - Add 4 Numbers\n\nGet ready for a tougher challenge! Four numbers will flash on the screen.\nMemorize all four numbers in the given time.\nWatch as the numbers fade away, leaving you to rely on your ninja memory.\nAdd the numbers together and input your answer to proceed.\nSuccessfully completing this level takes you one step closer to ninja mastery!\n\nLevel 3: Amateur - Add 5 Numbers\n\nThe stakes are higher as you face five fading numbers this time.\nSharpen your concentration and commit the numbers to memory.\nWitness the fading sequence and challenge yourself to calculate the sum.\nInput your answer and brace yourself for the next level of ninja arithmetic.\nConquer this level to prove you're on the path to becoming a true math ninja!\n\nLevel 4: Expert - Add 6 Numbers\n\nPrepare for the ultimate test of your ninja memory and mathematical prowess.\nSix numbers will flash before your eyes - memorize them in the blink of an eye.\nAs the numbers vanish, rely on your sharpened memory to add them accurately.\nType in your answer and see if you've reached the pinnacle of ninja mathematics.\nCompleting this level marks you as a true master of the fading numbers challenge!\n\nTips for Success:\n\n- Stay focused and keep distractions at bay.\n- Practice each level until you can effortlessly recall and add the numbers.\n- Challenge your friends to see who can achieve the highest level of ninja mastery!\n\nAre you prepared to embark on this mathematical ninja journey? May your memory be as sharp as a ninja's blade!"
            android:textSize="16sp" />
    </ScrollView>

    <Button
        android:id="@+id/btnBack2"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_marginBottom="36dp"
        android:backgroundTint="#00FF0000"
        android:fontFamily="@font/samurai2"
        android:text="BACK"
        android:textColor="#8f6233"
        android:textSize="40sp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintHorizontal_bias="0.497"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent" />

</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>
